When you register as a professional seller in the US, Canada, or Mexico, you'll automatically
have access to all of Amazon's North American marketplaces from a single account, making it
that much easier to introduce your product offers to a new pool of international customers.
This is called the North America Unified Account.
If you register as an individual seller in
the US or Canada, you'll still have access to both of those countries, but not Mexico.
The North America Unified Account lets you create and manage product offers, tailor your
listings, and manage pricing and inventory across the US, Canada, and Mexico marketplaces
from a single interface.
To quickly list your inventory across Amazon.
com, Amazon.
ca, and
Amazon.
com.
mx, locate the Expand Internationally Widget on the Seller Central home page.
Click
on Enable More Listings.
That'll take you to the Build International Listings tab.
Choose
your source marketplace, then click Connect Listings for each target marketplace in which
you wish to sell.
Select the target marketplace, offer type, and the pricing rules for your
listings, then click Save.
With that, all eligible listings in the source marketplace
will be listed in the target marketplace, connected using the pricing rule you selected.
Once you've connected your listings, you can exclude specific products from being listed
in the target marketplace, or adjust your pricing rules at any time.
Remember, you should
review and verify the listing information for each product you intend to sell in Canada
and Mexico, and exclude any offers for products you don't intend to sell.
Not all of the products
you offer in the US may be appropriate for sale in Canada or Mexico.
Be certain each
product you list complies with all applicable laws, regulations, and Amazon policies before
you offer it for sale.
For more information about North America Unified
Accounts, search "North America Marketplaces" in Seller Central Help.